https://www.preventdisease.com/home/privacy.shtml

Pictures on the Internet? Invasive Surveillance Awaits
MSG Lurks As A Slow Poison In Common Food Items Without Knowing
Avoid Ice Creams With Toxic Ingredients
Cure Tooth Decay Naturally By
Identifying The Real Cause of Cavities
Why is Glycemic Load More Significant Than Glycemic Index?
The 9 Personalities Which Are Changing The World
Everything Is A Lie: The Deliberate Intent To Deceive People Is At An All Time High
The Facts, Stats and Dangers of Soda Pop
Soy Lecithin: How It Negatively Affects Your Health And Why You Need To Avoid It
VO2 Max: How Fit Is An Athlete?
What is Acid / Alkaline Balance?
Hogwash Alert: One Flu Shot To Protect All Humans From All Flu Strains For Ten Years?
Awaken Your Brain: Coming Alive to Vibrant Well-being and a New Reality
Free Energy Is An Absolute Imperative For The Future Of The Earth And Humanity
How Dangerous Is Fluoride To Your Health?
Never Be Sick Again: Understanding Disease
Privacy
Statement
Overview
PreventDisease.com operates under the following set of strict
privacy principles:
The
only information PreventDisease.com obtains about individual
visitors to its Web site is that supplied voluntarily
by visitors.
Once
registered as a member, PreventDisease.com representatives
will NEVER request for your personal information, usernames
or passwords via email and any attempt at such a request
should be disregarded and ignored by any member.
In
cases when PreventDisease.com may need personal information
to provide visitors with customized content or to inform
them about new features or services, visitors are explicitly
asked for that information.
Personally
identifiable information provided by visitors (name, e-mail
or home address, etc.) will not be disclosed to ANYONE,
including any outside organizations, associations, corporations
or institutions unless visitors indicate that PreventDisease.com
may do so.
Only
statistical information about our visitors as a group
(usage habits, demographics) may be shared with any partner
of PreventDisease.com. Personally identifiable information
will not be shared at any time without the visitor's permission.
PreventDisease.com employs strict security measures to
safeguard online transactions; personal information is
stored in a secured database and always sent via an encrypted
Internet channel.
We
will notify our users if we make significant changes to
our privacy policy that may affect the use of health-related
information, and we will obtain consent from consumers
for any new uses of that data.
The following
discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices
for this Web site: PreventDisease.com.
IP
Addresses
An IP address is a number automatically assigned to your
computer whenever you access the Internet. All computer
identification on the Internet is conducted with IP addresses,
which allow computers and servers to recognize and communicate
with each other. PreventDisease.com collects IP addresses
in order to conduct system administration, report aggregate
information to sponsors and advertisers, and to conduct
site analysis. If a visitor requests pages from PreventDisease.com,
the PreventDisease.com servers enter the visitor's IP address
into a log. To maintain visitor anonymity, PreventDisease.com
does not associate IP addresses with records containing
personal information. However, PreventDisease.com will use
IP addresses to identify any visitors who refuse to comply
with PreventDisease.com's in-house rules or terms of service,
and to identify visitors who threaten our service, site,
customers or others.
Cookies
Our site places a text file called a "cookie"
in the browser files of your computer. Cookies are pieces
of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's
hard disk for record keeping purposes. Our site uses cookies
during your online session to deliver content specific to
your interests. Cookies allow us to avoid showing you the
same ad or other message repeatedly. Our cookies do not
contain personal information. They do enable PreventDisease.com
to relate your use of the site to information that you have
specifically and knowingly provided to our site.
Registration
Our site's member registration system requires users to
give us contact information such as their name and e-mail
address. The user's contact information may be used to contact
the visitor when necessary. The
user acknowledges that the member registration email address
provided, automatically entitles and enlists the user to
our free monthly newsletter as provided by our PD team.
The user can remove (opt-out) their email
manually through any page on our website. If at any time
users have been unsubscribed from the mailing list, they
may also choose to add (opt-in) their email to receive future
mailings; see the choice/opt-in section below for further
options.
External
Links
In order to provide visitors with greater value, PreventDisease.com
may provide links to various third party Web sites. However,
even if a third-party affiliation exists between PreventDisease.com
and that destination site, PreventDisease.com exercises
no authority over linked sites, each of which maintains
independent privacy and data collection policies and procedures.
PreventDisease.com assumes no responsibility or liability
for these independent methods or actions and is not responsible
for the independent policies or procedures of destination
sites. Similarly, PreventDisease.com cannot take responsibility
for the privacy initiatives or the content of such Web sites.
These destination links are provided only for your convenience,
and as such, you access them at your own risk. However,
PreventDisease.com wishes to ensure the integrity of the
PreventDisease.com Web site and its destination links, so
any comments pertaining to the PreventDisease.com Web site
or any sites accessed through PreventDisease.com links are
greatly appreciated.
Community
Partners
PreventDisease.com Community Partners represent well-respected
healthcare organizations across the country. Through these
partnerships, PreventDisease.com provides its Web site content
and services to enhance the Web sites of our Community Partners.
These sites also offer information about local healthcare
resources, thereby helping members of their communities
take active steps towards improving or maintaining their
health.
Surveys
and Questionnaires
Our online surveys and questionnaires may ask visitors for
contact and demographic information. The customer's contact
information is used to contact the visitor when necessary.
Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the
choice/opt-in section below. Demographic and profile data
is also collected at our site. This information is shared
with advertisers on an aggregate basis, but it does not
indicate the identity of individual users.
Contests
We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for
contact and demographic information. The customer's contact
information is used to contact the visitor when necessary.
Users may choose to receive future mailings; see the choice/opt-in
section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected
at our site. This information is shared with advertisers
on an aggregate basis, but it does not indicate the identity
of individual users.
Public
Forums
PreventDisease.com provides its users with chat rooms, forums,
message boards and/or news groups. Please remember that
any information disclosed in these areas becomes public
information and you should exercise caution when deciding
to disclose your personal information.
Security
The PreventDisease.com Web site has security measures in
place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the
information under our control. PreventDisease.com employs
strict security measures to safeguard online transactions;
personal information is stored in a secured database.
Children's
Guidelines
Some sections of PreventDisease.com may be designed specifically
for use by children under the age of 16. Contact information
such as their name and e-mail address, and demographic information
such as their ZIP code or age may be requested in those
sections. In such cases, children will be notified that
they should obtain permission from their parents before
providing such information.
PreventDisease.com
does not disclose personally identifiable information about
users under 16, whether or not an approval is obtained.
Information about users under the age of 16 may be shared
with third parties on an aggregate basis. Parents and those
permitting minors to use the PreventDisease.com Web site
should be aware that any information voluntarily given by
children in chat sessions, e-mail exchanges, BBS's, forums,
etc., may be used by third parties to generate unsolicited
mail or other contact with children.
Choice/Opt-In
Our site gives users the opportunity to opt-in to receive
communications from us at the point where the user registers
for a membership.
This
site also gives users the following options for removing
their information from our database in order to stop receiving
communications or our service. Choose one of the following
three options to successfully remove your email from our
mailing lists:
You
can unsubscribe your email from the left side interface
of any page on our website under "Free Newsletter"
and by inputting your email address, selecting the "Unsubscribe"
radio button and clicking the "Go"button.
You
can send e-mail to
You
can send mail to the following postal address:
Security and Privacy Dept.
PreventDisease.com.
P.O.Box 2087, SQ1 Stn
100 City Centre Dr.
Mississauga, ONT, L5B3C6
Canada.
...............................................................................................................
VIEWER RELATIONSAbout Us | Contact Us | Advertise | Terms and Conditions | Copyright Policy | Privacy StatementSTAY CONNECTEDNewsletter | RSS | Twitter | YouTube
| This site is owned and operated by PreventDisease.com © 1999-2018. All Rights Reserved. All content on this site may be copied, without permission, whether reproduced digitally or in print, provided copyright, reference and source information are intact and use is strictly for not-for-profit purposes.
Please review our copyright policy for full details.
aaa
InteractStay Connected With Our Newsletter
